I WANNA BE YOUR END GAME
I WANNA BE YOUR
FIRST STRING
I WANNA BE YOUR A TEAM
I WANNA BE YOUR END GAME
END GAME
BIG REPUTATION
OOH YOU AND ME WE GOT
BIG REPUTATIONS
AH AND YOU
HEARD ABOUT ME
OOH I GOT SOME
BIG ENEMIES
BIG REPUTATION
OOH YOU AND ME WOULD
BE A BIG CONVERSATION
AH AND I HEARD ABOUT YOU
OOH YOU LIKE THE
BAD ONES TOO
(FUTURE) YOU SO DOPE
DON'T OVERDOSE
I'M SO STOKED
I NEED A TOAST
WE DO THE MOST
I'M IN THE GHOST LIKE
I'M WHIPPING A BOAT
I GOT A REPUTATION GIRL
THAT DON'T PRECEDE ME
I'M ONE CALL AWAY
WHENEVER YOU NEED ME
I'M IN A G5
COME TO THE A-SIDE
I GOTTA BAD BOY PERSONA
IT'S WHAT THEY LIKE
YOU LOVE IT, I LOVE IT TOO
'CAUSE YOU'RE MY TYPE
YOU HOLD ME DOWN AND I
PROTECT YOU WITH MY LIFE
I DON'T WANNA TOUCH YOU
I DON'T WANNA BE
JUST ANOTHER EX LOVE
YOU DON'T WANNA SEE
I DON'T WANNA MISS YOU
(I DON'T WANNA MISS YOU)
LIKE THE OTHER GIRLS DO
I DON'T WANNA HURT YOU
I JUST WANNA BE
DRINKING ON THE BEACH WITH
YOU ALL OVER ME
I KNOW WHAT THEY ALL SAY
(I KNOW WHAT THEY ALL SAY)
BUT I AIN'T
TRYING TO PLAY
I WANNA BE YOUR END GAME
I WANNA BE YOUR
FIRST STRING
I WANNA BE YOUR A TEAM
I WANNA BE YOUR END GAME
END GAME
(ED SHEERAN) KNEW HER
WHEN I WAS YOUNG
RECONNECTED WHEN WE
WERE LITTLE BIT OLDER
BOTH SPRUNG, I GOT
ISSUES AND CHIPS ON
BOTH OF MY SHOULDERS
REPUTATION PRECEDES ME
IN RUMOURS I'M KNEE DEEP
THE TRUTH IT ITS EASIER TO
IGNORE IT BELIEVE ME
EVEN WHEN WE'D ARGUE
WE'D NOT DO IT FOR LONG
AND YOU UNDERSTAND THE GOOD
AND BAD END UP IN A SONG
FOR ALL YOUR
BEAUTIFUL TRAITS,
AND THE WAY YOU
DO IT WITH EASE
FOR ALL MY FLAWS, PARANOIA,
AND INSECURITIES
I'VE MADE MISTAKES AND
MADE SOME CHOICES
THAT'S HARD TO DENY
BUT AFTER THE STORM,
SOMETHING WAS
BORN ON THE 4TH OF JULY
OUR PAST DAYS WERE THE FUN,
THIS END GAME IS THE ONE
WITH 4 WORDS ON THE TIP OF
MY TONGUE, I'LL NEVER SAY
I DON'T WANNA TOUCH YOU
I DON'T WANNA BE
JUST ANOTHER EX LOVE
YOU DON'T WANNA SEE
I DON'T WANNA MISS YOU
(I DON'T WANNA MISS YOU)
LIKE THE OTHER GIRLS DO
I DON'T WANNA HURT YOU
I JUST WANNA BE
DRINKING ON THE BEACH
WITH YOU ALL OVER ME
I KNOW WHAT THEY ALL SAY
BUT I AIN'T
TRYING TO PLAY
I WANNA BE YOUR END GAME
I WANNA BE YOUR
FIRST STRING
I WANNA BE YOUR A TEAM
I WANNA BE YOUR END GAME
END GAME
BIG REPUTATION
OOH YOU AND ME WE
GOT BIG REPUTATIONS
AH AND YOU HEARD ABOUT ME
OOH I GOT SOME
BIG ENEMIES
BIG REPUTATION
OOH YOU AND ME WOULD BE A
BIG CONVERSATION
AH AND I HEARD ABOUT YOU
OOH YOU LIKE THE
BAD ONES TOO
I HIT YOU LIKE BANG
WE TRIED TO FORGET
IT BUT WE JUST COULDN'T
AND I BURY HATCHETS
BUT I KEEP MAPS
OF WHERE I PUT 'EM
REPUTATION PRECEDES ME
THEY TOLD YOU I'M CRAZY
I SWEAR I DON'T
LOVE THE DRAMA
IT LOVES ME
AND I CAN'T LET YOU GO
YOUR HAND PRINTS
ON MY SOUL
IT'S LIKE YOUR
EYES ARE LIQUOR
BODY IS GOLD
YOU'VE BEEN
CALLING MY BLUFF
ON ALL MY USUAL TRICKS
SO HERE'S THE TRUTH
FROM MY RED LIPS
I WANNA BE YOUR END GAME
I WANNA BE YOUR
FIRST STRING
I WANNA BE YOUR A TEAM
I WANNA BE YOUR END GAME
END GAME
I WANNA BE YOUR
FIRST STRING
I WANNA BE YOUR A TEAM
I WANNA BE YOUR END GAME
END GAME